<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>On with Kara Swisher (Blipped)</title>
    <description>It's on. Twice a week, award-winning journalist Kara Swisher gets to the heart of the story through no-holds-barred interviews with power players across business, tech, media, politics and beyond. So why do her guests show up? “Smart people,” says Kara, “like difficult questions.”
Mondays and Thursdays from New York Magazine and the Vox Media Podcast Network.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <link>http://nymag.com</link>
    <itunes:author>New York Magazine</itunes:author>
    <itunes:category text="Technology" />
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="https://megaphone.imgix.net/podcasts/d8dd4b8a-02be-11ed-9562-6bb84220205a/image/b3ee21e8c248e16d651e5048036a9b2c.png?ixlib=rails-4.3.1&amp;max-w=3000&amp;max-h=3000&amp;fit=crop&amp;auto=format,compress" />
    <item>
      <title>How Trump Dismantled the Department of Justice with Carol Leonnig</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f81b783c-d372-11ef-94e4-77019e598ffa-blipped</guid>
      <description>Under President Trump, the Department of Justice’s long-standing mission to uphold the law “without fear or favor” has been turned on its head. Attorney General Pam Bondi has followed Trump’s directives to target his political enemies and help his allies. But in their new book, Injustice: How Politics and Fear Vanquished America’s Justice Department, investigative journalists Carol Leonnig and Aaron Davis show that the erosion of the DOJ’s independence began long before Trump’s second term.

Kara speaks to Leonnig, MSNBC senior investigative reporter, bestselling author and five-time Pulitzer Prize winner, about how internal pressure campaigns in Trump 1.0 prevailed, despite the noble intentions of prosecutors; the many red flags that were missed by the FBI ahead of the January 6th Capitol attack; the stubborn bravery of unsung heroes in the National Archives Department during the Biden administration; and how the DOJ’s loss of political independence will impact the country.

Questions? Comments? Email us at on@voxmedia.com or find us on YouTube, Instagram, TikTok, Threads, and Bluesky @onwithkaraswisher.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <itunes:duration>3386</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 10:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://hulkling.tail166d96.ts.net/episodes/on-kara-swisher/How%20Trump%20Dismantled%20the%20Department%20of%20Justice%20with%20Carol%20Leonnig-blipped.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="127808826" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Scott Galloway Wants Us To Celebrate Masculinity, Not Diminish It</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f84050bc-d372-11ef-94e4-53b31a4f8655-blipped</guid>
      <description>Scott Galloway has spent the last few years ringing the alarm about how boys and young men are falling behind. Galloway, a marketing professor at New York University, best-selling author, and Kara’s ‘Pivot’ co-host, says his concern stems from the fact that he can relate to their problems. As a young boy raised by a single mom, Scott struggled in school, didn’t have many friends, and barely got into college. But he went on to found several successful marketing firms, make millions, and raise two sons of his own. He shares his story — and his own advice on how to be a good man — in his new book, “Notes on Being a Man.”



Kara and Scott talk about how the Trump campaign was able to win over young men with its regressive version of masculinity, why he thinks we need to re-embrace young men’s horniness, and why more men need to step up as mentors. They also talk about Scott’s difficult relationship with his late father, and the ways he’s trying to be a better father to his sons. 



Check out our sponsor Smartsheet here!



Questions? Comments? Email us at on@voxmedia.com or find us on YouTube, Instagram, TikTok, Threads, and Bluesky @onwithkaraswisher.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <itunes:duration>3503</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 10:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://hulkling.tail166d96.ts.net/episodes/on-kara-swisher/Why%20Scott%20Galloway%20Wants%20Us%20To%20Celebrate%20Masculinity%2C%20Not%20Diminish%20It-blipped.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="104142934" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons on Capitalism from Patagonia’s Reluctant Billionaire</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7f68b26-d372-11ef-94e4-a748aaf86f70-blipped</guid>
      <description>When Patagonia founder Yvon Chouinard first got into business, all he wanted to do was make better equipment for himself and his fellow “dirtbags.” Over 50 years, he built Patagonia into a global outdoor retailer with a sustainable mission and ensured that the company’s profits will go toward protecting the environment for years to come. 

In his latest book, “Dirtbag Billionaire. How Yvon Chouinard Built Patagonia, Made A Fortune, and Gave it All Away,” New York Times reporter David Gelles chronicles how Chouinard set new industry standards for sustainable production and charitable giving. Kara talks with Gelles about how Chouinard’s version of conscious capitalism compares with that of tech billionaires, what to make of shifting US corporate environmental and social responsibility, and how artificial intelligence could affect the climate in the future.

Want to see Kara and Scott Galloway live on the Pivot Tour November 8th-14th? Limited tickets are still available at PivotTour.com. 

Questions? Comments? Email us at on@voxmedia.com or find us on YouTube, Instagram, TikTok, Threads, and Bluesky @onwithkaraswisher.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <itunes:duration>3459</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 09:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://hulkling.tail166d96.ts.net/episodes/on-kara-swisher/Lessons%20on%20Capitalism%20from%20Patagonia%E2%80%99s%20Reluctant%20Billionaire-blipped.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="64482132" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judd Apatow on Meme Politics, Being Funny in 2025 &amp; the Comedy Biz</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7d18d1c-d372-11ef-94e4-036797892610-blipped</guid>
      <description>From an early age, writer, director, and producer Judd Apatow has been obsessed with comedy. What started as a quest to interview comedians for his high school radio station ultimately evolved into one of the most prolific careers in Hollywood today, with hits like “The 40 Year Old Virgin,” “Knocked Up,” and “Anchorman.” Now, Apatow is looking backwards. His new book, “Comedy Nerd,” is a visual memoir of his decades in the business, working with a who's who of the biggest names in comedy. 



Kara and Judd talk about how he reimagined the genre of raunchy, R-rated comedies about stunted adolescence; what he got right about American masculinity in the mid-and-late 2000s; and his recent pivot to making documentaries about some of the greatest comedians of the modern era. They also discuss whether AI can be funny and the ways politics is shaping comedy right now. 



Questions? Comments? Email us at on@voxmedia.com or find us on YouTube, Instagram, TikTok, Threads, and Bluesky @onwithkaraswisher.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <itunes:duration>3293</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 09:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://hulkling.tail166d96.ts.net/episodes/on-kara-swisher/Judd%20Apatow%20on%20Meme%20Politics%2C%20Being%20Funny%20in%202025%20%26%20the%20Comedy%20Biz-blipped.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="47714083" />
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>