<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>On with Kara Swisher (Blipped)</title>
    <description>It's on. Twice a week, award-winning journalist Kara Swisher gets to the heart of the story through no-holds-barred interviews with power players across business, tech, media, politics and beyond. So why do her guests show up? “Smart people,” says Kara, “like difficult questions.”
Mondays and Thursdays from New York Magazine and the Vox Media Podcast Network.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <link>http://nymag.com</link>
    <itunes:author>New York Magazine</itunes:author>
    <itunes:category text="Technology" />
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="https://megaphone.imgix.net/podcasts/d8dd4b8a-02be-11ed-9562-6bb84220205a/image/b3ee21e8c248e16d651e5048036a9b2c.png?ixlib=rails-4.3.1&amp;max-w=3000&amp;max-h=3000&amp;fit=crop&amp;auto=format,compress" />
    <item>
      <title>How Trump Dismantled the Department of Justice with Carol Leonnig</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f81b783c-d372-11ef-94e4-77019e598ffa-blipped</guid>
      <description>Under President Trump, the Department of Justice’s long-standing mission to uphold the law “without fear or favor” has been turned on its head. Attorney General Pam Bondi has followed Trump’s directives to target his political enemies and help his allies. But in their new book, Injustice: How Politics and Fear Vanquished America’s Justice Department, investigative journalists Carol Leonnig and Aaron Davis show that the erosion of the DOJ’s independence began long before Trump’s second term.

Kara speaks to Leonnig, MSNBC senior investigative reporter, bestselling author and five-time Pulitzer Prize winner, about how internal pressure campaigns in Trump 1.0 prevailed, despite the noble intentions of prosecutors; the many red flags that were missed by the FBI ahead of the January 6th Capitol attack; the stubborn bravery of unsung heroes in the National Archives Department during the Biden administration; and how the DOJ’s loss of political independence will impact the country.

Questions? Comments? Email us at on@voxmedia.com or find us on YouTube, Instagram, TikTok, Threads, and Bluesky @onwithkaraswisher.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <itunes:duration>3386</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 10:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://hulkling.tail166d96.ts.net/episodes/on-kara-swisher/How%20Trump%20Dismantled%20the%20Department%20of%20Justice%20with%20Carol%20Leonnig-blipped.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="125608270" />
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>