<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>The Vergecast (Blipped)</title>
    <description>The Vergecast is the flagship podcast from The Verge about small gadgets, Big Tech, and everything in between. Every Friday, hosts Nilay Patel and David Pierce hang out and make sense of the week’s most important technology news. And every Tuesday, David leads a selection of The Verge’s expert staffers in an exploration of how gadgets and software affect our lives – and which ones you should bring into yours.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <link>https://www.theverge.com/the-vergecast</link>
    <itunes:author>Vox Media Podcast Network</itunes:author>
    <itunes:category text="Technology" />
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="https://megaphone.imgix.net/podcasts/e4c412e6-e1f0-11e8-9bde-83f9d376f059/image/Podcast_Tile_6000x6000px.png?ixlib=rails-4.3.1&amp;max-w=3000&amp;max-h=3000&amp;fit=crop&amp;auto=format,compress" />
    <item>
      <title>Version History: Fire Phone</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1c87406-97ea-11f0-8c9e-3f3acfb4ab03-blipped</guid>
      <description>In 2014, the tech world was abuzz with the prospect of a phone made by Amazon. When the Fire Phone arrived, it was chock full of ideas — a "dynamic perspective" feature that created 3D illusions, an image-recognition feature called "Firefly," and many, many opportunities to buy Amazon products. Allison Johnson and Sean O’Kane join David Pierce to discuss why, unlike Amazon's successful e-readers, this device was a gigantic flop.

If you like the show, ⁠⁠subscribe to the Version History feed⁠⁠ to make sure you get every new episode.

Subscribe to The Verge⁠ for unlimited access to ⁠theverge.com⁠, subscriber-exclusive newsletters, and our ⁠ad-free podcast feed⁠.

We love hearing from you! Email your questions and thoughts to ⁠vergecast@theverge.com⁠ or call us at 866-VERGE11.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <itunes:duration>4973</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 10:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://hulkling.tail166d96.ts.net/episodes/vergecast/Version%20History%20Fire%20Phone-blipped.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="76757826" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring back the iBook, you cowards</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">113d247a-d358-11ef-8041-afef74412bcd-blipped</guid>
      <description>The DoorDash problem just became Amazon's problem. Perplexity's Comet browser is allegedly stealthily shopping on the internet's largest mall, and the folks in Seattle want it to stop. It's just one example of the fast-moving power dynamics on the internet, as AI companies try to change the way we search, shop, and do everything else. Lots of companies are not going to settle for being dumb databases, and Nilay and David discuss how this fight might play out. After that, the hosts talk about the reports of an impending cheaper Mac with an iPhone chip, and whether that might mark Apple's true return to consumer laptops — or be something else entirely. Finally, in the lightning round, they talk Brendan Carr, late-night shows, party speakers, and sonic logos. Lots and lots of sonic logos.



Further reading: 


  Amazon and Perplexity have kicked off the great AI web browser fight 



  WEB WAR III 



  Apple is planning to use a custom version of Google Gemini for Apple Intelligence 



  OpenAI launches its Sora app on Android 



  
Perplexity is going to power AI search in Snapchat. 




  Easier access to AI Mode, if that’s your thing. 



  
Google Gemini’s Deep Research can look into your emails, drive, and chats 




  Google Maps taps Gemini AI to transform into an ‘all-knowing copilot’ 



  Amazon is building Alexa Plus into its Music app 



   The AI industry is running on FOMO 




  
Apple is reportedly working on a cheaper Mac laptop with an iPhone chip 




  iOS 26.1 lets you tweak Liquid Glass, and it’s out now 



  YouTube wants a piece of the late-night TV pie. 



  Apple TV’s new name now comes with a new sound 



  Brendan Carr votes to eliminate cybersecurity requirements



  Epic and Google agree to settle their lawsuit and change Android’s fate globally 



  I’m amused by how Google is complying with the Epic injunction. 



  xAI used employee biometric data to train Elon Musk’s AI girlfriend 



  Into the Huluverse: The sonic evolution of Hulu




Subscribe to The Verge for unlimited access to theverge.com, subscriber-exclusive newsletters, and our ad-free podcast feed.We love hearing from you! Email your questions and thoughts to vergecast@theverge.com or call us at 866-VERGE11.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <itunes:duration>6529</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 10:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://hulkling.tail166d96.ts.net/episodes/vergecast/Bring%20back%20the%20iBook%2C%20you%20cowards-blipped.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="160201078" />
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Version History: Zune</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1b3b8a4-97ea-11f0-8c9e-a31de8fbd080-blipped</guid>
      <description>In 2006, Microsoft came for the iPod's throne with an innovative MP3 player called the Zune. It had a bunch of features the iPod didn't: WiFi, music sharing, a bigger screen, a beautiful UI, even an FM radio. And to hear Microsoft describe it, it was even kind of a social network. Nilay Patel and Victoria Song join David Pierce to break down why, despite all that, the Zune never really took off. And why it came in brown.

If you like the show, ⁠⁠subscribe to the Version History feed⁠⁠ to make sure you get every new episode.

⁠Subscribe to The Verge⁠ for unlimited access to ⁠theverge.com⁠, subscriber-exclusive newsletters, and our ⁠ad-free podcast feed⁠.

We love hearing from you! Email your questions and thoughts to ⁠vergecast@theverge.com⁠ or call us at 866-VERGE11.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description>
      <itunes:duration>4638</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 10:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://hulkling.tail166d96.ts.net/episodes/vergecast/Version%20History%20Zune-blipped.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="70052508" />
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>